Well, a sister put up a video where she was standing outside Tyler Perry Studios and saying that she wants him to pick up her show that she shot.
And I put in the comments, you know, he doesn't pick up shows that aren't his, sis.
And you should see the backlash that I got for saying that, which is just a basic fact.
But this was my favorite response.
There is nothing respectful about anything you say, especially to our black men and women.
Yeah, I know how you do.
I think for me, my marvel is always in just the level, not just the level of hatred that I'll get from other black people,
but the level of hatred that is unsupported by facts, completely irrational and illogical that I get from black people.
Anywho, sis who put up the video is actually very funny.
And so, you know, good luck to her.
But her people and her comments are trash.
And I want to take this moment to thank y'all on my page because there's always a level of respectfulness,
of intellectualism, and of straight up love that be showing up in my comments.
And I appreciate it.
But back to this.
Respectfully, what the f*** are you talking about?
With that said, make sure you listen to my radio show, The Amanda Seals Show on radio and wherever you get your podcasts.
And you can hear my other podcast, Small Doses.
And now you can watch it on YouTube at AmandaSealsTV so that you can see me be respectful to black people in everything I do.
Happy Black History Month.